Hello there everyone. How are you?
>> Doing good. Doing good. How about
yourself?
>> Just fine, sir.
>> Sir,
>> I'm having I'm having a great time
actually.
New therapy
changes are being implemented. So, I am
very happy camper right now.
Oh, I'll be right back. I'm let people
get in.
I'm back. I'm like slim shady.
I'm back. I'm back.
What do I need for class today?
So, I don't know if any one of you guys
make beer bread, but I bake beer bread
every week. And um if you ever do it,
Guinness
and um Japanese abies
make some make some really like amazing
beer bread. It's like phenomenal.
So I made it today with AB and I just
man that was some good stuff. Oh
sometimes I make it with Guinness.
Guinness is just incredible. Just saying
you guys do it that way. All right. See
how many people we got in the room.
Wow. Leavarius. How's your uh how's your
Waffle House shift going? We liking it?
>> Pretty good, man. I got a seat seat
reserved for you.
What would that say?
>> Okay.
>> And buttermilk covers, you know, covers
uh the the chicken and waffles cuz
that's the way Theo likes it.
>> I ain't doing no chicken and waffle. No,
no. Chicken and waffles do not go
together. ready for you, man. Come on
through.
>> Stop. Sacrilege. We're not going to do
that. No. No.
>> That's right, Theo. Give it a shot.
>> What about waffles and chicken?
>> No. No. That doesn't go together either.
No. No.
No. We don't do that. No. Waffles are
only go with sweet things, not with
protein. No.
>> What?
>> Scrambled eggs.
>> Sweet and sour chicken.
>> No, the breakfast. Okay. The eggs are
different. That's different. We're I'm
not talking about like chicken, steak,
stuff like that. No, we don't do that.
>> So, you never had steak and eggs.
>> Steak and eggs, but there's no waffles
in there.
>> You put waffles to the side?
>> No. No, no, no, no, no, no.
If I have steak and eggs, there's no
waffles or pancakes involved.
>> So, you don't have no cars on the side
of it?
>> What?
>> You don't put no cars to the side of it?
Not. It's not steak and eggs. No man. No
man. It's protein protein man.
Protein freak on
>> some asparagus. I do with some tomatoes.
Um green pepper. Something like that.
>> That's
>> Is that Hopson in your background Jay
with the uh motion?
>> Oh, someone someone caught it. Someone
caught it.
>> I saw it.
>> I love it.
>> Hold on. Who said that? Who said that?
Who said that?
>> That was me, bro. I re the most racist
video of all time. It was hilarious.
>> Oh, man. What you know about that, man?
>> What you know about my guy with the
white contacts?
>> Bro, I don't know nothing about him
except this this this video.
>> Oh, that's Oh, this is the Oh, this the
only video, you know? Oh man.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh man. But yeah, that's him. That's
him.
>> Before I put my face on it,
>> I need you to get your um
get your consoles open. This week we're
doing um what is it? Doing clickups. I
need to demonstrate some things for you
guys first as a concept. These are a
little bit more complicated and I need
make sure you guys get this right. Okay.
So
everybody open up your console. I'm
going to show it to you from here. You
can see my screen, right? You good?
>> Yes,
>> sir. We can see it.
>> Good. All right.
>> Y question.
>> Hold on. Look. Somebody got a question.
>> Yeah. Did you uh modify the meeting with
the passcode by chance?
>> No.
>> No. Okay.
>> All right. Thank you.
>> You guys were lucky. Um, I was too busy
to implement that, but I had to hope to
God that you guys did your homework. I
had some guys panic sending me
communication regarding homework. I was
like, I wonder what's going on. I didn't
remember what I had said, but I
remembered it later on this afternoon.
But I was like, uh, I don't I don't have
the organization in place to to to
enforce it
>> actually. Yeah. On that note, honor, can
you fill out the sheet, drum, I think I
saw you here.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I got something to add. I
got some
>> I Well, I see I see repos, but I don't
see anybody marked.
>> Oh, okay.
>> Oh, okay. Let me let me read it again.
Let me check out what I'm missing. I got
you. Like you see how TIQS does his so
green the highlights mean they did
submit it like I mean ideally like so
you guys don't have to copy it every
week. I would just put everybody's repo
down and just like do what's in the
template and then just highlight them
and uh that way it it's like the same
and you guys don't have to find repos
each week and stuff.
>> All right. But they put like people
might be put in a new repo every week.
So, I don't know. I don't know. Maybe
they should stop doing that, but um
>> uh it's it's up to you. Um
>> All right, cool.
>> For for the homework, I don't care.
Like,
normally, I would say uh
for the submissions, whatever is easiest
for you. Like,
>> but I mean, if it's really obvious what
they name their repos for the homework,
I I could just look at their GitHub
accounts and look at the recent rep.
>> I'll do it. I really just if it's if
they have a repo in this week, that's
that's a submission.
>> Yeah. Second.
>> Yeah. if they as long as they're naming
it something coherent and like you know
class 7.5 like I'm seeing
>> uh someone their repo class 7.5 week
seven that easy enough
>> all right
>> yeah just just to make it easier on you
guys I don't want you guys having to
track down repos different repos every
week
>> yeah all right cool
>> appreciate it Anyway,
okay.
>> Recorded.
>> Yeah, go ahead. Record. All right. So,
this week we're going to start with um
what we call an instance template. Okay.
Move first instance template and then
we're going to do something kind of
Soviet. It's going to be really fun. I
like Soviet stuff. Anybody here like
Soviet stuff? Communistic stuff?
you know, we're having problems with
socialists, so I thought we'd do
something with them this week. So, first
we'll do instance groups. Okay. So,
instance group, sorry, not instance
group, we're going to do um instance
template. So, what we've been doing so
far is deploying
um what last few weeks we've been
deploying infrastructure with Terraform
and that's great. That's really good.
there is something we can do kind of
similar not entirely somewhat kind of in
an automated fashion to deploy an EC2 uh
we still have to use click ops just that
it's less click ops okay so we're going
to make an instance template this is how
we do it right so first we're going to
go to compute engine
okay
I don't have any compute engines right
now right and I need to make a
>> inm Guys, it's he he's it he's always
going to say that.
>> What?
>> He said EC2.
>> Oh, guys, get used to that.
>> Don't Don't be missing the master race,
bro. You
>> I could I could say EC2, VM, ASG,
VPC. Who knows? I say VPC all the time
for sure.
>> Or the but but some people this is their
first quest with you, Dio. tough. Get
used to it. If you go to the office,
this is how we talk.
>> I'm going to Where's your Where's your
baseball bat?
>> I I got it. It's down there.
>> Yeah, Julian.
>> Okay. Yeah.
>> Anyways. Anyways, a server is the same
as a VM
virtual machine is the same as a EC2,
which is which is what a server is in
AWS land.
You guys will learn this as you continue
your studies because the cloud cloud
technologies and cloud infrastructure
copy themselves across different
environments. They they may be called
different things but it's ultimately the
same thing. You study enough and then
you'll see the similarities. But for
now, VM is the same as EC2, which is the
same as a server, which is what you guys
have built out with that uh with those
scripts that they provided you earlier
on in the class.
All right. So, see over here we have
instance template right here. I need you
to click on that.
Now, over here says create instance
template. Click on that.
Now, we can go ahead and give a template
like we just give it a name for example.
So, what I'm going to do real quick is
I'm going to go over here to this
superscript. I'm going to do call this
and we'll call it super a. So, I'm going
to get rid of this real quick. We'll say
super a. All right.
And it's regional Iowa. And just like we
did before, it looks pretty much the
same thing. I'm going to scroll down. We
don't keep everything the same as
before. Okay. And we'll keep everything
the same as before. And um we allow and
remember for the firewall as normal we
need to allow HTTP.
Okay. And go through here. Remember has
again the boot disk, right? Same stuff
as before. Go to advanced options. We'll
go to networking just to make sure. I'm
going to put this into the default um
VPC. Remember, for network tags, it
needs to say HTTP server right here.
This is an important thing.
It does need to say this because if if
it does not, it means that you did not
click this. All right. So, this tag is
like for the firewall. This is actually
very important. So, firewall allow HTTP
traffic and then the tag will appear.
All right.
I go down here and it says your network
interface. Just make sure that you are
in your default VPC.
I am right now. Good for me. I'm going
to go ahead and scroll down here a
little bit more. I'm going to go to
management
and see how it says here it has
automation and startup script. Right? I
want that startup script. So, I'm going
to go over over here to my um GitHub.
I'm going to go to super a.sh. Okay. We
did this before.
and going to all done. Go ahead and copy
this.
Go ahead and put it over here. Paste.
There we go.
All right.
And
that's all we need to do. There's really
nothing else
over here that I need. This is it. This
is good enough. Okay. So, we'll go ahead
and create it.
and
all this. Well, it's not done yet.
Okay. And I now have a this is a
template. So, this is basically the
instructions about how to deploy an EC2.
Okay.
So,
all right.
We good.
I want to make sure everybody has done
this.
Okay. So, please take a screenshot.
Okay.
And put it into the chat.
Make worse.
Where is my
there?
Just so I know you've done it correctly.
Hey
was the path to the script again.
>> Yes,
>> you should have as is the first link. Y
got it. Thank you.
Okay,
good. I like what I see, guys.
Let's see what you got here.
Okay.
Yeah. Yeah, that's that
that's correct, Aaron. Yeah. the the
diagram that Aaron put into the chat.
Make sure you guys download it because
that's what's coming down the pipeline,
but I'm not giving it to you yet.
It will be in my notes as well in my
repo.
Okay.
Okay,
good guys. I like what I said. I like
what I see so far. All right. Now,
see how it says here VM instances. Go to
VM instances.
I'm going to say create instance.
Going to say create VM from
instance template.
I go here and choose super A.
Okay.
Isn't that fast?
Now I want to make sure that I can SSH
into it. See if it works.
Wow.
Wow. Look at that. SSH works.
Go ping 8.8.88.
Wow. Look at that.
Look at that.
It worked.
Okay. Next.
See, it has external IP right there.
Same as before.
Go ahead and get that
http col.
Boom.
It's working.
Was that nice?
So, you can go ahead and copy that.
Copy the link. You can put it into the
chat. Oops. Make sure you you put it as
a proper link,
not just the IP. And then I can see if
you're doing your work or not. Kevin.
Kevin was doing. Kevin, what you got?
Yeah. Oh, Kevin did it. Kevin wants that
cloud job.
Michael, did you do it?
Michael wants the cloud job.
Ernest.
Ah, Ernest wants a cloud job.
William.
William wants a club. Uh, wow. Yousef.
Good. Thomas.
Oh my good. Look at all these people who
want cloud jobs.
Hey Rob, should we allow all these
people to get cloud jobs?
Oh no.
>> Is not allowed. I I look Look at all the
Kishas who are going to lose husbands
because of this. Oh my goodness. Oh, all
these guys. Carlton's going to be so
rich.
He could afford to go to the homeland
and buy a wife there.
One of Just so you know, one of the guys
in the mix, I think he went to Ghana. I
think it was Ghana. I don't know. It was
either Ghana or Kenya. I forgot. and he
met a woman, paid $50,000 dowy and got
her because she's a virgin.
He says like,
>> "I know that guy's African."
>> Yeah. Yeah. Then he's uh very happy.
>> Not having any problems.
>> Irwin. Irwin, you you came back to
class. You participated and you did the
Ed and you did the stuff. My good Irwin,
what's up? I thought you were supposed
to be poor and dusty.
>> Oh, no. No, not at all.
>> I thought you were supposed to be poor
and dusty, Irwin.
>> Oh, brother. No.
>> I thought you're supposed to be like,
you know, just like I don't know,
>> flipping burgers, trash collector.
>> Hey, no, I can't do that.
>> Don't you lay up with Kha for that for
that tax return?
>> No, bro. I can't do it. I gota steal my
purpose.
Y'all still on purpose?
>> Oh my goodness. I thought you Okay,
Lavarius.
Order, please.
>> Check.
>> Can you hear me?
>> Yeah, I can hear you.
>> Okay. U I kind of stepped away at the
beginning. So, the first thing you made
was a instance template, right?
>> And did you choose EC E2 for um the
Hold on. When I when you make an
instance, do I choose anything?
>> Um,
I know you just changed the network and
I'm not sure.
>> Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. Let's go
back. I want you to think.
>> Okay.
>> So, when I make a create an instance,
do I choose anything here?
>> No, you don't choose anything there.
>> Ah, so why would the instance template
be different?
I don't know.
It's pretty dependable. It's pretty much
default. It's if you start thinking like
computers are like the computing systems
are but it's different here versus
different. Okay, this is not Azure.
Okay, in Azure you can start. Okay,
there's some [ __ ] up things in Azure
that don't make sense. But GCP
>> GCP and AWS tend to be like a little pro
like I don't know engineer like they
don't want to be moronic.
>> So
pretty much the same all the time.
>> Okay. So for the firewall did you choose
allow HTTP traffic or at HTTPS traffic?
>> Okay. though why would we choose why
would we change our process?
Okay. So it should be HTTP then since we
never chose HTTPS then
>> if we do HTTPS what's necessary?
>> We got to change port.
>> Well that is we have addort but what
else is necessary?
>> I don't know.
You have to have a cert
443.
>> Okay.
>> So if we're have I if I haven't talked
about search generation in class yet,
right?
So we can't do 443 cuz that's a whole
headache.
>> Okay.
>> When we when we when you actually start
doing 443, you'll be like damn.
Okay.
>> Okay. So yeah, we're not we're not even
doing anything like that. Um, okay. What
you got?
>> So um I'm still at the part where you
create the instance template and I went
ahead and copied the user script.
>> Where exactly am I supposed to paste
that? Because I'm looking
>> Where did you paste it at before?
in the startup script.
>> Yeah, the startup script. Uh I'm looking
at advanced options.
>> Okay. So, go to there.
>> This security management soul tendency.
>> Okay.
So, I want you to try to figure out
where you would go.
I want you to figure it out because
you're smart. You can do that.
thing I see that looks like
it could uh accommodate that would be uh
management.
And there's the there's a big box there,
but it says description.
>> Is that right?
>> Is is is that the only option?
>> Uh there's security, which I know that's
not it.
>> No, no, no. I want you to think
what you're saying. Basically, if I go
to create instance,
>> it's like you're going to create
instance and you think all of the
options are only right here on this
screen right now and your your thumb you
cannot use a mouse. Your fingers are
broken suddenly.
I I want you to get out of this thinking
because something's wrong up here and
that you need to know understand how to
scroll and look for options.
You should always know how I see it.
>> Scroll down. Ah,
>> I see. Okay.
>> Ah, okay.
>> It's under Okay. It's under management
automation startup script. Okay.
>> Okay.
>> Automation.
>> Okay. So, I got that.
>> Why am I getting on you on this? Reason
is is because if you're doing Terraform,
Terraform is going to have is going to
know as a as a declarative language. So
it's going to a GCP and declaring where
to put the script and even in Terraform
startup. That's the we know it's
startup. We're declaring that. And so if
I go to like right now in the VM here, I
go to advanced. I'm looking for
automation startup script. This is here.
Why would it be any different with a
template?
It's not. It's the same thing. You just
have to look for a box that says
template. So, if you saw a description,
you should say, "Oh, I'm probably in the
right place. I just need to keep on
looking." And they keep on looking.
This isn't Azure.
If you ask that for Azure, I'm down with
that. I totally get you cuz Azure has
some [ __ ] up navigation that is gooey.
It's messed up here. GCP. Nope.
It's
boring nerd predictable.
You want chaos isa level computing
Azure. That's going to happen like we're
going to do that later on the course.
You're going to see Azure be like, "Oh,
GCP was pretty easy. All you got to
think or do is do a think about a
process. That's all. Pretty intuitive.
Azure is like,
yeah, you okay, let's just gaslight you
for no reason. All right.
>> Right. Okay.
>> So, so once I do that and I create the
uh template, I just go to the next step
is to go to template uh instance
templates, select the one I just
created, and then go to actions, click
on the three dots, and create VM. And
that'll create the
>> create instance.
Create instance create from
>> and then instance template. And then you
choose a template.
>> Well, okay. So create.
>> Okay. I clicked on.
I don't see the create. Where' you see
the create from? Oh, right here. Okay.
Create VM from instance template.
Select it. Create
>> or you want to do if you want to
customize it, you can. I'll customize
another one in a second.
>> One right now. Okay.
>> Okay. I think it's creating one. Okay.
It's creating now. It's just taking a
minute.
Good.
Okay. Got it.
This take a while cuz it's not
the external IP I put in there in the
browser is not working.
Browser.
>> Yeah.
>> What? Wait. What are you talking about?
Browser.
>> The external IP address that I got that
was generated.
>> Oh, okay. Okay. Okay.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. You know what to do.
>> Yeah. It just says it's it's okay. It
worked. I got it.
>> There you go.
>> Okay. I remember that that that user
script takes a while to do. It's why I
did SSH first.
So I knew that engine X was starting up.
Okay.
There you go. Albert. Good.
Alex. Alex Felder.
Hold on.
Good.
Jack.
Daniel.
Good.
Richard.
Good. Jay Herrera. Good Sean.
Good.
Dromo.
Good
bass cloud.
Good. You know, you could always swim
across a pond, declare yourself a
refugee.
>> That That doesn't work right now.
>> You should try it.
>> Oh, that No, you Aaron's correct. Uh I
won't bore you but worked I'm working I
got a proono lawyer at my job explained
to me the whole process they're shutting
that they're shutting the the refugee/
asylum pipeline down
>> even for big booty Latinas Rob
good
>> I my vote is we could keep that open I
mean
>> yeah okayella Good.
Okay. Yata.
We'll see what we do.
Yana, good.
That's pretty good. I didn't have to use
you as a teaching tool at all today.
You're doing better, Yana. I like that.
Okay.
Good job, guys.
I'm just saying the big booty Latinas
they should get refugee status like no
problem. I have no problem with that.
>> Wait wait wait. But hold on.
>> I I'm I'm a fan of this. But let's game
this out. You want big boy blue latinas
to come here but we but you but we want
to leave. So that means all the big blue
latines are here but then we
>> No, no, there's still there's still
there's some some over there too. Oh,
okay.
>> Think of it like this.
>> High quality big booty Latinos want to
stay in Latin America
about America.
>> If more big booty Latinos come over
here, that's a denial of service against
Western women for marriage.
>> Listen, big booty Latinos and petite
Asians.
>> Yeah, that's what I say. Bring them
over. Yeah. Just to deny. So they so
western women are like, "Damn, the local
guys are marrying the foreigners and the
passport bros are leaving to get better
foreigners. Now we're pissed. Nobody's
coming over to bang us." Like, "Yep,
that's right, woman." Anyway, okay. So,
enough.
>> Nothing left to do but for them to lose
weight. I guess
>> even I don't care. I don't care if
Western women are super models. I'm
still No. Nope. Nope. So, nope. Not
going to happen. Okay. I'm not saying
for us, but you know the guys who are
left behind.
>> Good.
>> They were alone together.
>> Okay. So, we'll go back to compute
and I'm going to go to my VM right here.
I'm going to go ahead and tear that down
real quick. Okay.
Uh, delete.
Okay. now.
So, delete your VM. Let's say that I
want to make three instances.
How can I do this?
We're going to do, watch this. Create
instance.
Create VM from instance template.
I'm going to choose super a customize.
Okay.
Now, where is it?
Where is my
working? Data protection. No backup.
Advanced networking. Hold on.
Let's see. Where is
Where is it?
Where did I
shield type standard?
There should be a number here.
Unless I totally got this one wrong.
There's no contain container. Nope.
Nope. Wow. Okay. Uh, okay. So, we can I
thought for sure there was here. Okay.
So, I got that memory wrong. Okay, fine.
>> What are you looking for?
>> I'm looking for number of instances.
>> Number of
You're creating an instance though,
>> right? Right. But you should be able to
say I want like three or four of them at
one time.
>> Are you creating it from a template?
>> Yeah.
>> I know AWS and Azure can do this without
a doubt. So I thought for sure I had
done this before in GCP. If when you're
doing this,
>> I've never done that. Yeah.
>> You're just like boom, I want this
number and it gives you the number.
Uh okay. So I was
um
>> custom under machine type.
>> Keep scrolling down.
>> Oh no, that's was a course.
>> Okay,
>> let's go down.
No,
no, no. That those are course
standard.
>> According to Google, you have to do it
from instance groups.
>> Yeah, that's the only way you're going
to do it in scripts. That sucks.
>> I guess technically they would count it
as an unmanaged instance group.
>> Okay. Yeah, that's So yeah, that sucks.
They shouldn't do it that way cuz what
if I if I don't that
that's a little controlling. Okay.
Anyway, let's not do this then. All
right. So, what we're going to do next
is MIG. Okay. So, this is a manage
instance group. So, basically what we're
going to do is now say if we want to
create a number of VMs, how do we create
the VMs? And then also how do we get it
to unite together as one unit. Um, so
one of the beauties of the cloud is
something that we call scaling.
To scale means to automatically
provision
uh resources based upon demand. So
demand goes up, you make more resources,
you utilize more resources and if demand
goes down, you decrease your resources.
So it's just basically on demand. That's
it. On demand is one of the best things
we can have, right?
Hold on.
Okay.
All right.
Okay. So, all right. So what we're going
to do is look we're going to look at
instance groups and then also just go
directly to manage instance groups. The
manage instance groups is the best thing
we can do and manage instance groups is
where we get the fun and the beauty the
starting and the beauty of the cloud.
Now you guys in the other class you guys
did ASGS which is the same thing as make
all right manage Instagrams means make
that's where I was talking about
something sulkate. Okay. So to make an
instance, go to manage instance group.
Just say managed.
You can do MIG. Actually, you'll
probably find it. I didn't care. You
have instance groups here or create a
MIG here. Okay. So I'm going to say
managed.
Okay.
You can do the tutorial for this. I
don't want this. I want
I don't want wait where is my
No, this is I don't
There we go. Let's just do this. Go to
compute and compute go to instance
groups. Okay.
Okay. I'm going to go ahead and create
an instance group.
Hold on. What are you guys talking? Uh,
don't don't don't don't pay attention.
Okay. So, create instance script.
>> Focus on your instance groups.
>> You're being a distraction. Yes. Ignore
us. No. I
>> Come on. You got you got you got
students that want to get more cloud
money deal. Come on.
>> Okay. All right. So, I'm going to call
this MIG one.
Okay.
Um, ASG in
GCP
and it's going to count X here for
instance template because you've already
done the instance template. Here it is.
Let's say number of instances. I'm going
to say three.
Okay.
And now it's going to say location.
Could say a single zone or multiple
zones. Now this is kind of an important
thing. Listen up. Please pay attention.
If you put all of your instances into
one data center, which is one zone,
what could the potential problem with
that be?
>> Well, there's a case there's a there's
an issue.
>> It would be like recently where the data
center went down because we had to
replace like a bunch of nodes at XAI.
>> No redundancy.
>> Yes.
This is why
>> when Iran was sending drones against one
a I was laughing. I was like ah because
if they did it correctly they they could
lose that entire genocide. I don't care.
We got other ones. So send them over.
We're going to bomb you to death. Okay.
So I'm going to do is say multiple. And
it's going to say which zones do you
want to use? And it gives you some
options. All right. You can choose as
you want. If you want to do more, for
example, if I want to do four
instances,
okay, can choose that as you want. I'm
just giving you guys options. Okay, so
here we go. Four. I'm choosing four
zones. Okay, now target distribution
shape is going to be balanced. This will
be normal. Just do balanced just by
default. Let's say autoscaling. Yep. say
VM instance life cycle
repair on instance yes autohealing
all this stuff just keep it as um
default there should be oh okay we we
got to create a health check all right
so here and this is the fun this is
where the fun starts okay so health
check
okay you you have to do the health check
there's no other way I remember this
okay so go over here create health
check.
Okay, I'm going to call this MIG one
health check.
You notice how this is always really so
boring and predictable. This is exactly
the way competing is supposed to be
boring and predictable.
Okay,
now I'm doing scope. It's going to be
regional
Iowa. That's right.
Okay,
logs. I'm going to turn on the logs.
Okay. And down here, I'm not changing
anything out down here. You notice how
all this other stuff is pretty much by
default. All I did is give it a name,
copied the name in the description. The
scope was regional, and I turned on the
logs. That's all I did. Nothing else.
Okay.
Go ahead and save this.
Uh, fine.
Okay.
Uh,
I don't care. It's a lab. I'll keep it
there. All right. Initial delay is going
be 300 seconds. Uh, default action. Just
say default action is fine. Keep the
same instance configuration. Yes. Yes.
Oh, yeah. For now, I'm just say keep the
save instance configuration. Uh
just do default. Keep it at default
here. Change zone during v in repair. Uh
allow this is by default. Keep it there.
Okay. Don't do anything there. All
right.
So all we're doing I'm doing four uh
instances. I'm adding um autoscaling
which is be nice. Okay.
And what I'm saying here is update
instance configuration. So basically
this is for in case you change your
template. It's going to to apply the
most recent template to the new VMs.
It's kind of a fun thing to do. Okay.
And the port mapping we don't need
anything to do here. Okay.
So I'm going to go ahead and create
Wait for that.
Yes, Rob.
>> Question for you.
If you had,
let's say,
let's say B Rica gym becomes a global
phenomenon and now you have
$300 million play work.
>> No, no, no, no. Stop. Stop. Stop.
>> Stop.
>> No. That's like saying, "What if you
banged a 24 a 21-year-old playmate
>> AV girl?"
>> No, no, I don't go there. My mind
doesn't entertain such ideas. I've got
I'm probably not going to have anything
more than $5 million at the end and I
have my gym and I have some dogs. That's
it. I don't want to think about anything
else.
>> Yeah. No. If I I might make the AI
company, might make a few million there.
>> A few.
>> It really is Theo in some apartment
someplace with a dog eating a quessle
and reading the newspaper. Is it
not going to be high level Theo?
I'm not like that.
>> I high level Theo is no more.
>> Nope. No. No. No. I mean, I might I I
wouldn't mind making the the high level
uh
>> high high proficiency in skill set.
Sure.
>> The AI the AI company. Yeah. But
>> right but high visibility field is
that's never happening.
>> Nope.
>> Well, that means Okay.
Okay.
No, no. I um
therapy.
>> I I don't Hey,
>> cortisol.
>> That that is fat is I I was want to ask
if if is if if you will want to if you
if you if you had the the bread, but you
but if you don't want the bread, if you
don't want that level of money, then
that's understandable.
>> No, I really just want to make um a few
albums.
um with electronica
for stuff certain genres I want to make.
Uh and then
>> do some weight house parties.
>> Yeah, I like to go to some like decent
parties. Um get my weight under control.
Um reduce read all the psychology books
I'm supposed to read on therapy books.
Um
get I want to be like a really great
with Cisco again. want to be really
great with AI doing that kind of stuff.
But to be honest, I just want to ride my
bike, sit down in a park someplace and
either have some quason or some empadas
or something like that. Play with
Chewbacca. That's it.
Flat
>> life. I like that.
>> Just basic
nothing more. Just I did it. It's kind
like right now my favorite part of the
week is
like Sunday morning I wake up at 6 and
there that's kind of funny. Okay,
there's a 247
Mexican restaurant I go to and at like
6:30 7 o'clock in the morning all the
everybody who's drunk and all the
strippers are in there. So I go there, I
just have breakfast and I read this is
energy flash. Okay, this book is energy
flash and it's a history of electronica
and it starts with um Detroit. It was
what the Detroit sound was. We're going
through the history of it and I sit
there and I have my breakfast. It's a
Mexican breakfast. I sit there like
watch strippers talk about what happened
to them. Like they they sit there, they
talk about it, right? So I just I listen
in and I just read this book. That's my
that's that's my moment of the whole
week. I get on my bike and go back home.
That's so low key.
I might sit there and uh plan out some
more gym equipment that I want to buy.
That's it.
Okay.
All right.
So, when's your when is your border room
appearance going to be?
>> Border room.
>> Border room. the uh the DJ sets.
>> I have one part here, then the other
part being over here, and I hope to get
it done this summer,
and there's so many things going on this
summer, and I'm kind of irritated that I
can't just be a hole in the wall, but I
have to get things done. And then
um I have to go to the Netherlands.
So, at least the the mobile music set
that the mobile music
Uh, what can I say? DJ setup is I have
it. I can whisk it on the airplane. So,
that's good. But I can't bring my 808 or
909 over there. It's not going to
happen.
So, I have to be three months without my
gym, too. It's going to suck.
All right.
So here you guys see here we have a
managed we have a managed um uh instance
group. Okay, here we go. Manage instance
group and has health check. Here we go.
All right. So what I do is take a
screenshot of this and I want you guys
to take a screenshot to show that you
guys did it.
Um, Jerome, you think that vocabulary
word is coming out of my mouth?
There's some I I that kind of syllable
structure. No, I don't say words like
that. That's not Slavic.
It's not Japanese.
Thought I heard it. I'm sorry. I was
listening halfway.
>> Oh no, you got something going over
there.
Okay. Yes, Xavier rave. It It actually
is very much rave culture. I'm actually
going to go there to to study um DJing
and how they did sets. I'm totally
surprised to what degree my music
preferences were were influenced by the
Netherlands. I had no idea it was that
big, but it's major thing,
right?
Okay. So, you got that. Now, what you
have here is you have your external ID
IP address right there. So, you can go
through here and look at each instance
if you want to. So, here for example,
I'm going to go over here and HTTP
There you go.
There it is. Okay.
So, this is the manage instance group,
right? This is kind of a big thing. All
right. So, before I continue on, does
anybody have any questions?
Came in late. Theo, I don't have the the
template.
You have to make the template.
Make what? Make the template. Guys, have
let's have you guys do this. Have Okay,
John, I want you to share your screen.
And guys in the class, I want you to
tell him how to make an instance
template.
Got
you. I show you.
>> Hello. Hello. Hello.
>> Can you hear me?
>> Hello.
>> All right. Go to
Hold on.
>> Hello. Hello.
>> So, X out of that. Create C create an
instant. Oh, no. Okay. You good?
>> Yeah, you're good. Oh, that works too.
>> Yeah. Go. Go back to that create instant
template.
You see the second one?
Yeah.
No, no, no. Not instant group. No,
instant template.
All right. Look on the side. See virtual
machines. And the second one. Second
one. Next one.
>> Yeah, that one.
Check, check, check. One, two.
>> Okay, cool.
Okay, so you going to rename it
whatever you want. All lower case.
Okay.
Um, keep going down. You going leave
that. Keep going.
Keep going.
>> Keep going.
>> Change it.
>> The bottom.
>> Okay. Allow TTP traffic.
>> Yeah.
>> Keep going.
>> Advanced options.
>> Yeah. So you get the um
>> and
management
>> and where it says startup script, you
would go to the repo and get one of the
startup scripts. Since you got super as
the headline, just get Supra,
Super, you know, whatever.
Yeah, same thing.
create.
And while that's booting up, you can go
to uh
instant groups. Type in instant groups
at the top in the search bar. Bash, you
forgot to record.
Well, people going to be crying over
this one.
>> Oh, damn. You see that? It say see where
it says instant groups.
Click that one. Yeah, that one.
Yeah.
Yeah. Don't It don't don't matter. Just
click one. Yeah. Yeah. All right. Create
instant group.
Okay. So, we going to name this one uh
MIG1. Sorry.
And then
>> this meeting is being recorded.
>> Name MIG1.
>> And then you're going to go to number of
instances. You're going to select four.
>> Okay.
>> Scroll down.
>> All right. Multiple instances.
>> Multiple zones. You'll go to the zones.
And
>> since you have four, just go ahead and
click that one, too.
>> Yeah,
>> scroll down.
>> I don't think we can figure out auto
scale. Okay.
>> Got to go to the health check.
>> Create Yeah, create a health check.
Yeah,
>> there you go.
>> Then name it
>> MIG1 health check. One word.
>> Yep.
>> And do the same thing. Put a
description.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. You going to change it to regional
next
>> scope and regional.
>> Select logs on
and save.
>> Save.
>> Yeah. Leave all that default.
>> Yeah.
>> Create.
>> Go ahead and create, baby.
>> No. No.
Oh, you got to scratch me.
That
>> the most important part.
>> Yeah, man. We slacking, bro.
>> Yeah, as long as you know.
>> Yeah,
>> all right, baby. Just wait for it to
load up.
>> And when it's done creating, go ahead
and click on that um instance group.
Just verify that you have all four and
they're working and you should be all
right. Yes, sir.
Yeah. Give it a minute.
>> Yes. Is it still loading
or running?
>> You see that little blue like saying
it's loading up. So stand by. He doesn't
have that check mark.
screenshot and put in the chat.
Hey, John Omar said he got a crispy ass
goatee duck.
If uh Jay Herrera still lost, he should
share the screen and get some help.
Hold on.
Okay.
Name it MIG.
All right. All right. It doesn't really
matter. MIG health one health check.
Uh, put the same thing for description.
and regional for the range.
I don't know if it matters, but you name
it MIT health check. It should be MIG1
health check. Name and the description
should fix that too. Name it the same
thing.
Okay.
Okay,
>> hold on. Why does it have to be MIG?
>> Man, it's an interest in group. I think
>> I named it that, but does it have to be
that?
>> No.
>> He just doing a health check. It doesn't
have to be that thing.
>> Does the name and the description have
to be the same or no? You just do that
to make your life easier.
>> Okay.
>> And so it don't get lost in the sauce.
>> Yeah. And logs on.
>> Logs on.
>> Then save.
>> Yep.
>> Yes. savior. That was coming, but I
didn't feel like it yet.
>> Then just create
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Do Did you
pick the the um the health check? Yeah.
Yeah. Okay, then you can create then.
The health check is right over I Oh,
here it is.
>> Yeah. Yeah, you create it now.
H
I think I'm supposed to wait a sec.
Yeah, it takes a second.
I don't know if it's getting the
exclamation point about say you should
probably let's see let's see let's wait
see it say updating so let's give it a
second but I think it might be a problem
says 0% healthy
Okay, maybe. All right.
I don't think I changed the number of
businesses.
>> Oh, you probably didn't now that I'm
thinking about it.
He said four, didn't he?
>> I don't think we scrolled up uh to see.
>> Oh, yeah. We just went to health checks.
Yeah, you're right.
>> What's causing that?
>> Excuse me.
>> The um autoscaling was configured
because I ran into the same issue. So,
what I would do is I would delete that
instance group and then remake it. But
this time, don't configure the
autoscaling.
How many zones you want?
>> I think this the one he uh already has.
I think we're going to delete this one
and create another one.
>> I just tried to edit it. Um
hope that doesn't break it.
>> Give it a go. See if it's a mutable
setting. It's
>> saving right now.
Did I break
H
you delete that joke
I say. So still give it a second. The
other one had that too.
>> Fair enough. So remember guys, so the
health check it it's a
>> it's a probe that's going to send
requests on port 80
>> right
>> to your web web server and if the web
server doesn't respond that's when it
thinks it's unhealthy. But when we're
making a VM does it instantly work?
>> Nope.
>> No.
And when we when you created more uh
VMs, did you change any other settings?
>> No.
>> So they'd be identical replicas,
>> right?
>> And see now it marked it as healthy
because it finally finished
bootstrapping and stuff.
>> It worked.
But whenever when I did it, it had those
uh little circle little red circle this
time, I guess, with the exclamation
point. Kind of made me think it was
going to it was already broken. Yeah, we
saw that on the first one they had that,
but after like a couple refreshes, it
went back to uh green. So, as Aaron
said, it probably just needed time to uh
make sure everything was good.
Mhm.
Still good.
I can destroy it now, right?
>> Stand by.
>> You need to you need to keep it up for
about two months.
>> Two months. I don't know if I got um two
month instance money.
>> You got money like that.
>> I know you do.
>> I'm broke boy. Broke boy right here.
>> You're not broke. You're not broke. You
are rich.
>> You see these girls? You see these girls
in the back? That was the last of my
money. All right.
that see you you can see you you have
you have money for women that means you
have money for computers
>> I know
>> I know you got money you're rich
>> so does that does that mean you're
sponsoring all of us with free buddy
>> for all these I I pull poor I poor
>> a come on
>> no money for the women I don't have
anyone to
>> broke boy
>> broke boy broke broke and dusty that's
what I am broke and dusty
>> hey a class I tried
>> okay so let's go and tear that down real
quick. So, let's go over to instance
compute and then go to instance groups.
Okay,
>> tip for today.
>> Do it again.
>> Oh, no mouse
>> and got to do it one more time.
>> Okay.
Trying to make things a little easier
this week.
Okay, we're just going to start again
at instance at um instance template.
Okay, now
you can have fun with instance
templates. All right, so if you go over
to GitHub real quick,
let's go back over to GitHub, right?
It's not that. No, let's not do that.
It's not. Come on. Give me my GitHub.
Okay. So, you notice that there's a lot
of startup scripts, right?
>> Right.
>> So, what you can do just to make things
easier if you want is you can just like
say basic right here. Let's just I'm
going to show you how to how I would do
this. Actually, this is how I was going
to teach the class originally in the
beginning, but I thought the other way
was kind of more fun. All right. So what
you do is again for people who just came
in
um go to Google cloud here
go to compute engine and then go to
instance template right here okay take a
screenshot of that if you want to okay
screenshot it
I can't I want to move this right we'll
go and take go to instance template then
create instance template
Now what I'm going to do, I'm going to
call this basic. Okay.
Now everything through here is normal.
There's nothing you have to do. Go all
the way down to the bottom and hold on.
Do do this though. Allow HTTP traffic.
Make sure that firewall configuration is
there. Do not mess with that. So allow
HTTP traffic is there. Advanced options.
Go to management.
We have starter script, right?
So you just go over here to basic,
copy it,
paste.
Okay, great.
So now we have the basic. Now just go a
little do this around the circles.
Basic a
copy.
Same thing. Create instance template.
Get rid of this.
Boom. Basic A. Scroll down.
Make sure you get the uh H allow HTTP
traffic. Advanced options
management.
Startup script.
Go back.
Copy it.
See, it's the same thing every time. You
can just do that with all the starter
scripts and you have all the startup
scripts right there as templates,
right? Create.
See, isn't that easier?
Then you don't have to think about
GitHub. Let's do it again. Create
instance.
Go over here. Basic B.
Did I call it basic B? Really, Theo?
Okay, there. Basic B. Scroll down.
Same thing again. Allow HTTP traffic.
Scroll down.
Advanced management
automation.
Do it again.
Basic B. Copy it.
Boom. Done.
So that see what I mean? It's you're
literally doing the same thing again and
again. Now, why would I do this besides
teaching you guys is that when you're
making the manage instances, manage
instance groups or when you're doing
other things later on, if you want to
use one startup script versus another,
it's now it's already in there. You just
have to go there and just take it from
there. Oh, you take it the template.
It's simple. It makes your life easier.
That's all I'm thinking about. Okay.
Okay. Hold on. Let's see what you guys
are saying in the chat. We want your
leisoc script. I don't have enough.
There's not enough buffer size for the
leoscript. I'm sorry. We can't. It
doesn't the There's not enough room in
all of Google compute for the leoscript.
It doesn't have enough space.
Put it on blockchain. No. No. No.
Yes. Me are boring without LB. That's
right. I decided to do the instance
scripts and then do LB later on. I want
to do to tell you the truth. I want to
do like global.
I I want to do regional. I just want to
do global. Makes my life easier. Um I
want to do it Baron's way. Baron's way
was correct. Regional is so boring.
Might as well just do region. You might
as well just do global. Um anyway,
so did everybody do that? Did some
people do that? Do you guys have some
instances?
Take a screenshot of your instances just
so I can see if you guys are doing this.
Not if you want to name it your Liso
instance, you can. I don't care what you
name it. Okay, just have fun. I just the
reason I named it there cuz that this
these are the names of the of the user
scripts. That's it. It's so that I can
remember it. That's all. What do you
got, Gregory?
>> Uh these instances like free or do we
have to tear them down at the end of the
>> instance template?
>> Oh, that's what I meant template free.
Okay, cool.
All
right.
>> Anyway, okay, kids. So, some of you guys
got it. All right.
Okay. So, guys, make sure you guys get
this. I mean, and I make sure the people
who didn't do this last hour, do it now.
I want to make sure all of you get this.
That was good, you guys.
I don't know. I'm just particularly
cruel this like this that this time with
the manosphere like we basically won.
Like instead of celebrating and being
nice, I'm like going for blood. I'm
really just I I was like Theo, you
savage. Why do you
Anyway,
we broke. We ain't got it. We broke.
That's right. We broke.
That's right. We don't have without the
service. We got to go to Black IT
Network.
Stop. Stop it. Stop. Be good. Be good.
Okay.
All right.
Who's in the class? Make sure
everybody's in the class.
See here,
Kelly did it. there.
TQS ts.
>> Alonszo, where are you? Oh, there you
are. Christopher, make sure you do this.
>> Yeah, try right now. Okay,
>> this is big. You can't get to the next
section without doing this template.
as I'll be happy. I had a
troubleshooting call at 5:'lock this
morning and guess what? I couldn't go to
sleep last night until 4:00. So, I got
one hour of sleep.
I'm kind of loopy right now.
I'm still going to enjoy going to sleep
tonight. It's going to be great.
Bob, I like that screen. I like that
screenshot. I like what you have there
on the profile photo. Good.
Yes, Bash.
Good, Bash. Good. Okay, so I'm making
sure I go through this all again because
the looks like part of the first hour
wasn't recorded. So, I'm just gonna just
making sure I do it all through here.
>> I think Jules recorded it.
>> Hopefully, he did. I mean, he's here in
his little bot thing is
>> okay.
Yay.
the right
book about me. Like half of my students
were AI cloud engineers speaking full
fully fluent Japanese. Suddenly for some
reason all these black guys are speaking
Japanese in Japan
called Chewbacca running.
Oh, you're funny. Okay.
Okay, Irwin. Good.
Okay, good. Okay, so you guys got the
template. This template is totally
necessary. You got to get template,
>> instance group or instance template.
>> So what you first do is go to Google
Cloud
and then
here
Google compute engine and then instance
template.
then create instance template.
Okay. What I'm going to do is go over to
GitHub.
I'll do your father. Well, no, your
father too works by far better. Okay,
let's put this into the chat
for shits and giggles.
Let's put here.
Okay.
So, this one's called Your Father Tube.
I'm going go and copy name here.
Go over here. I'm going to name my
template
your father too. This is a regional. You
scroll down. There's nothing to change
here.
Then firewall allow HTTP. The same as
making instance as before.
Okay. Advanced options. Scroll down.
management.
You have automation startup script. Go
back over to
uh GitHub. Copy.
Copy the script. Go back over to here.
Paste that over into
uh the start script area. You got a blue
button here. Create.
It's all it is. Just make it a template.
All right.
Oh, yeah. You can.
Yeah, you could do that. Yep. Yeah, you
could do that, too. Yep.
Yeah. Yeah.
What I actually want to do, to be
honest, one of the things I'm going to
do later on is um I want to get some
like games or fun things in the user
script and then you can like choose
which game you want to load in something
like that. Like there's other ideas I
have for user script. I'm just trying to
figure out what to do there. All right.
Says everybody made user scripts because
you can't do the MIG without the user
script. So, did
>> Sorry, the um what do you call it? I
needed like a two factor verification.
He tried to block me. I just I just
fixed it right now.
>> Oh, okay.
>> Okay. Did you get the template?
>> Did the template right now and then now
I have to do basic B, right?
>> No, no, no, no. Just one. Just one.
That's all it needs.
The reason why I did it multiple was to
reinforce it as a learn as a teaching
tool. You only need one. That's fine.
>> So, I'm in uh basic B right now. No, not
basic B. I mean a create instance
template. Then what do I click on?
>> If you if you did you make one template?
>> Yeah, I created an instance template.
>> Yeah. Did you make one instance
template?
>> Yeah. Oh, you want me to change the
name, right?
>> No. Oh, no, no, no, no. You can't. Yeah,
you you don't have to. Notice here on
this one, I didn't change it,
but you can. It's easier for you to
remember if you change the name.
>> Mhm. So,
>> Leo Contra game. Oh man, you I don't got
enough compute power for that.
So then I have to copy
and create.
>> What is it? Copy and create.
So again show it to you one more time.
Okay. Create instance template
here. Okay. Going over to GitHub.
Calling this your father.
Copy
name here.
Paste.
Scrolling down.
Where do you copy and pasteed that again
from the GitHub? I'm in my GitHub right
now. So you're following
>> user scripts. A user script.
Yousef. No. No. Oh, man. You Oh, man.
You
I'm just I'm just trying to teach. Be a
nice teacher.
Okay. Okay. Now, scroll down.
Okay. Okay.
>> And mine says Lutheran W user script
main. Copy paste that.
>> No, no, no, no. I didn't do that.
Right here.
>> Okay. So, sample
sync
branches up to date. Contribute sync
fork.
sample script two.
>> But you don't have to copy this. You can
just write it out if you want to. I'm if
I'm pasting and I'm doing this, I'm
showing how easy it is.
Just trying to make it as easy as I
possibly can. You can just write it out.
Whatever whatever whatever is best for
you.
Okay.
>> Then all you do is scroll down
and
go to firewall. You allow HTTP traffic
as you do normally with a template.
Okay.
And then here at advanced options, you
click on that.
Go to management.
Scroll down. See, it has startup script
right there.
We'll go back over to GitHub.
Going to copy this.
Go to GCP. We're here. Paste.
That's it.
It's very It's very simple. All you're
doing is copying and pasting. literally
and and clicking said so like for the
I'll show you how many how many changes
there were. So there was one copy one
paste
scroll down scrolling
two the one click
then going back over to here another
copy and paste. So two copy and paste
and you put that in there and then
create. So basically you have five
actions in order to create a template.
It's all five. Nothing more.
And then you go ahead and create.
You only have to do it one time.
I'll just show like I don't know why
this like mine doesn't look like yours.
Hold on. I'll put in the chat.
Oh, I like that.
>> Chewbacca has a message for you at the
bottom.
>> Yeah. I don't know why mine doesn't like
look like that in the user script. I put
in the chat
>> because he knows how to play with the
user script. That's why. I don't care
what the user script looks like. The the
whole thing of copy and paste is to make
sure you know how to copy and paste.
This is what I'm usually I'm actually
doing. I'm trying to make sure if you
can I'm trying to test if you can copy
and paste. If I don't think you can copy
and paste, then there's a problem
because then I I know you can't do
terraform.
>> No, but the Lutheran you told me not to
use the Lutheran web user script. Like
can't I shouldn't cut.
>> Hold on. No, no, no, no, no. This is the
It should be in Balorica AI.
This is the one we've been using right
through here.
You might use another one, Lutheran W
for another area.
>> I was using Bellerica boss. Hold on.
>> But this is where for this class is what
we're using. Well, this is what I'm just
You should have um for the first class,
you should have taken this.
So, I'll go ahead and put back into I'll
put it back into the uh
Yeah, that Pocahontas.
Yeah, it's nice.
I'll do that.
Yeah, I still
What is this one? I don't know what this
one is. Oh, yeah.
What's this over here? I don't know what
this is over Oh, what's this over here?
This is my favorite.
>> See, Rob has been trying
>> to your father.sh
or your father?
>> Anyone? It doesn't matter.
is to make sure that you can do it at
least one time.
Don't overthink it. Basic. Just do it
once.
You don't have to do it all the times
that I did it. So, I'm the I'm the
teacher. I do this multiple times, but
you as a student should make sure you do
it at least once.
>> Then, all right, I copied your father.sh
and then now
made a template.
Yeah, I made a template already.
>> Good. All right. So, next we're going to
go ahead and make a compute. So, let's
uh actually let's just go make the
manage instance groups. Okay. So,
go down to
sorry on compute
and it says instance groups. It says
instance groups right here. Click on
instance groups.
Okay. Here it says create instance
group.
Okay.
Okay. Now
instance groups you can put any name you
want here. So tempted
by toollet.
There we go.
And
copy this and put this in the
description. All right.
Now when you get to this point it's
going to say notice how it says instance
template.
Now these are all the templates that I
have. If you have basically all the
instance templates that you made are
going to appear here. You can choose one
that you want. I'm going to choose your
father too. All right.
Next
number of instances I'm going to choose
four.
Okay, my goal I got to wait for it to
start up.
Okay,
now I'm going to do is
Okay, location single zone. Click single
zone.
So mine is Iowa. My default is Iowa.
And I look at these zones here and I
have four zones.
Okay, good. That's what I want.
It has all four there. Now, what that
does is it puts Yes. multiple zones. It
puts one VM in each zone.
So, in case one data center goes down,
it doesn't matter. You've got three
others.
This is why I laugh at Iran.
Or we got your data center. Woo. We have
two or three others in the same region.
Go ahead, [ __ ] Yeah. Oh, we have uh
B2s. We know how the directory of that
little thing you sent over.
There we go. Look at that there, Kirk.
Oo,
every time I like this and very good
job, Kirk. Very good job. So, just press
create, right?
>> The template.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You got to do that, girl.
You can't.
>> Yeah, you can't. You don't have an
option.
>> Didn't you had it on single zone?
>> Yep. Single zone.
>> I thought we were doing multiple. Okay.
>> Oh, sorry.
No, m No, no, sorry. Uh, multiple zone.
>> Weren't you in the middle of
explanation?
>> Yeah.
>> Sorry. I thought I thought it was
region. Sorry.
lock asleep. So
location is going to mean we have
multiple zones and there we go. That's
there it is. So we have all four zones
checked here and that means we're
putting the uh VM one VM in each zone.
This is what I want and your
distribution shape is going to be
balanced. Okay.
Okay.
Now
we're going to do autoscaling.
Click on click autoscaling.
Okay. Then on and add more or instances
to the group. So what autoscaling is is
the ability to provision and um remove
VMs based upon traffic or if something's
if a VM is healthy. So for example, if
something is wrong with your VM for
whatever reason it happens to computing,
what the autoscaling group can do with
the health check, which we're about to
do, is it can say, "Okay, we don't like
this
like we don't like this um like the the
health of this VM. There's something
wrong with it. So let's just tear it
down." That's what it does. It just
tears it down and it brings up a a new
one, a healthy one. That's exactly what
you want. It makes life a lot easier.
It's It's like if you're using two Macs
and one of your Mac is like mine is
messed up, it just automatically does a
reconfiguration of the machine.
Nice. Wish I had that. Okay. Autoscaling
is after you created the instance
template.
>> Yeah. Yeah. We're in
we're in creating instance group.
So if I go back over here, okay,
all the way down here in the bottom, we
have instance group
and then create instance group.
Okay,
I'm going to call this um
to
proc.
Okay, there we go. Copy this. Put it
here. And see how it says here instance
template.
If you made the instance template, then
it it appears here. If you didn't make
an instance template, then you have no
options here. Remember that.
So, I'm choosing your father too. But
you can choose any tense template that
you want. You're free to do what you
want.
Okay.
Number of instances is going to be four.
Scroll down.
Location,
there's multiple zones. Iowa
and I'm choosing all four zones in Iowa.
This is going to be B. Don't do anything
here. Balanced.
Now I'm going to go over here to
configure autoscaling.
Okay.
The default is just just just keep the
default. Don't do anything here. Minimum
number of instances I'm going to do one.
Maximum number of instances is 10.
That's fine. Keep it there.
Okay.
Autographing signals. It's autoscaling
signals. Keep it there. There's no
reason to add a signal.
That's fine. Schedule. Don't touch
anything here. Don't touch anything
here. And
VM instance life cycle.
Don't touch anything here. That's fine.
Okay. What you do need to touch is auto
healing.
So we go to auto healing. We're going to
need to make a health check. I already
made a health check before. Make a new
health check. Okay.
So do create health check.
I'm going to call this
Dr.
Chewbacca
BM.
And all I'm going to do is copy this
name and put it into the description.
The reason I'm doing this is because
it's just easy to do. Just a process.
You can name it. You can put anything
you want into the description. You can
copy war in peace and put it in there.
All right. Scope regional.
Region is Iowa. Scroll down. It It
should auto auto do this for you.
Logs. Yes.
Now, health criteria.
It wants me to change this one. So,
check in interval. going to do 300
seconds for the check interval and the
timeout
is going to be 300
healthy threshold
uh consecutive successes. So two and two
that's one right that's it
and then you come here and press save.
Oh, that's fine. Put 300. That's good
enough.
Okay. So, this is 300. Default action is
fine.
There's nothing to do through here.
That's it. Says allow repair the VMs in
the alternative zone. Yes. Update
instance configuration. Yes. We're not
touching anything through there. Okay.
What you got?
>> Yeah. Okay. Um, on the one I just did
now for number of instances, it's grayed
out. It won't let me select it. It says
it says based on autoscaling
configuration.
So I'm looking at autoscaling.
Is it because I have maximum number of
instances set to 10?
>> No. No. Cuz
>> so I thought you put four there. You you
you
>> Yeah, he put the four, but when you hit
auto scaling, then it blacks it out
because the four was
>> Yeah, then it blacks it out. That's
right. And then you you can you do the
number here.
>> That's fine.
>> So, you're basically you're basically
setting the number down there and
autoscaling.
>> Yeah.
>> And it overrides.
>> Yeah. That's overrides and overrides.
Continue going. It's like stop the
compute.
>> Gotcha.
We don't tie, we multiply.
I like that. That's a good one. Okay.
All right. So, all we do is scroll down
here. So, again, the bottom is create
You're not sharing your screen.
I What do you mean? Can people see my
screen?
>> We can see you.
>> Can see We can see your screen.
>> Yeah, I can see it.
>> See?
Addicted to chocolate right there. This
is This is Rob's influence. He's either
trying to get me to go back to Japan or
do Afro Afro Venezuelan again. Something
like that.
>> I don't like you. You need to figure out
what you want to do. Okay. Don't Don't
make up the Afro Venezuelan steel.
That's not even your flavor.
>> I want another Wookie. That's all I want
is another Wookie.
>> Okay. Go find yourself a Go make
yourself a redhead out in Scandinavia.
I don't need to scan a name again. We
can't trust them.
>> Just uh screenshot this, right?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, we can. So, it has here this time
it only has here one instance. That's
fine. That's name.
There we go. Now, in this case, yeah,
this is normal. It's being verified.
Don't worry about this. Okay. Um we have
here the autoscaling is is definitely
being working.
Okay. So, let let that be. Don't don't
worry about this.
It'll it'll take a little while for this
thing to work.
Again, your template it has, as long as
it has the template in there and it's
saying it's been created, well, good.
That's all that's all going to work.
Deal with
all right.
What you got?
Good.
Yeah, you did fine. Doing fine.
Yeah, Chris, hold on. So, you did good.
I do like pancakes.
I do. I love pancakes. Not only do I
love pancakes, I love American pancakes
in particular. I love I've been all over
the world.
I love American pancakes. They're the
bomb.
>> You like the fluffy Japanese pancakes?
>> No, no, no. I love I love generic
American maple syrup.
>> See, I'm down with it.
>> But you'd love um the Japanese pancake
if you had chicken with it.
>> No.
Imamo
guys know
>> they need to invent fluffy Japanese
waffles.
>> Yeah, you guys need to start doing like
have like AI doing translation of what I
say in class cuz if you guys know what I
say sometimes you're like whoa
you are Japanese.
Didn't know you were that Japanese.
Um real maple syrup. Oh, can I like the
Canadian maple syrup, too. Don't get me
wrong, when I was in Japan, we got
Canadian maple syrup. Like, that's what
I normally had. But when I flew to
America,
had my suitcases empty. It came back
with coffee that I bought in America and
de deodorant,
Twinkies, and maple generic American
maple syrup. M.
I visited Japan. They I noticed that
their desserts are not as sweet as ours.
Do they have something?
>> Thank God. That's They don't have
diabetes. They don't get fat.
They don't have cancer. They don't have
the teeth problems that we do.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. That's maybe we should follow
that.
>> Agreed. Agreed.
>> Oh, don't touch American Sprite.
>> Sprite.
I know. Sprite is only Sprite if it
comes from America. I just learned this
the hard way. I have never You go over
there and it's like their their real
Sprite is like diet Sprite or Sprite
Zero or something.
>> They have um what is it? So even the
Doritos are different. Doritos are
usually different in every country
basically. So we'd have to of course you
have to Doritos imported from America,
right? Like what what costs like $2 bag
here is like $10 in Japan. Did not care.
crack. Oh, loved eating Doritos there.
Oh, so good.
Oh, Doritos.
>> I think the stuff that rots your teeth
is the high fructose corn syrup. It's
not the actual real sugar.
>> Sugar. It's sugar. It's sugar. Yeah, the
sugar. You know, the stuff that our
ancestors had them to make in the in the
plantations. Yeah. That's Yeah, that's
what kills you. Sugar.
So the Japanese don't have in their
products.
They enslaved us so that they can make a
drug which rots their teeth.
>> So what do the Japanese use for
sweetener in their products? Cuz it's
different.
>> Um no,
>> they don't.
>> They don't need to.
>> They use actual fruit and they make
paste out of actual fruit. Um fruit,
>> you know what I mean?
>> They don't need to make it sweet.
>> Fanta is yellow.
Okay.
>> Yeah, it takes a little while to get to
detox, but then once you get used to it,
you're like, "Oh, yeah. Why am I going
back?" It's still hard for me to deal
with American sweets.
I I don't I do not like
Nope.
It's too much.
Yeah. Andre said Doritos in Columbia
taste different. That's right. But
Doritos in every country tastes
different.
All of them.
That's why you have to get the American
ones imported. Somebody just had his
hand up.
>> Yeah, it was me. In Japan, they have
what what type of toothpaste do they
use? So, I heard their their teeth are
far far better health than what we have
over here. And I don't use fluoride.
>> Hold on. No, no. It's not because it's
because of their diet. They don't eat
sugar.
>> But they use a special type of
toothpaste also, don't they?
No,
no.
There is a dentist in the 1800s who just
went around studying people who eat, how
their people ate like all over the
world. So he'd go to Japan and watch how
Japanese people eat or he'd go to like
different parts of like Papa New Guinea
and watch how they ate and take pictures
of their teeth. And in places where they
never heard of toothpaste, they they
didn't have toothbrushes or whatever,
they had perfect teeth because they just
ate a particular way.
>> No sweets. Probably
>> no sweets. That's what it is. It's no
sweets.
>> Well, that's boring though. No
chocolate.
>> No. No. You You could have chocolate.
You just don't have that much sugar into
it.
Rob's having a little too much fun
there. I wouldn't mind that. That That
looks good. So, yeah, just don't put no
sugar in it. But here, like this. Okay,
Dr. Pepper. Zero sugar.
Okay. Don't need sugar. Stop the sugar.
>> So, is like a virtual machine like is
that like an emulator? Because I use
something similar to that with my VPS.
No, it's a computer.
Same thing. It's on emulator. It's a
computer.
But you're going to figure out, you're
going to find out later on what it
really is. That for now though, it's
just a computer. Just think of it like
that. It's a place where you can use an
OS. So if you want Dave, if you want
Microsoft, you want another OS, this
environment allows you to use that OS.
you really want to get technical, it's a
container for an OS,
but we don't want to go down that path
yet.
>> I've seen people have a Microsoft 11 and
then they had like virtual machine for
Linux.
>> Yeah, but that's on your desktop, right?
>> Desktop, laptop. This is this is the
this is the cloud. So you can make
multiple you can multiple OS choice
choices. Let me show you. Okay. So let's
go over here to VM instances. Right.
What I do create instance
just to give you an example.
Let's go to OS and storage right here.
Notice it has Davian.
Davian right? Davian, GNU, Linux 12.
Let's go and change that.
Operating system. Look at all the
operating system options that we have.
All these options
we can go through here. Look at all the
suffering we can have with all these.
Oh yeah. Yeah. Let's make sure I never
get laid again. Let's go do that one.
Okay. Let's do show one more of 12. Oh,
Windows server.
Now we have the version. We have all
these versions of Windows we can run on
here.
Right? So you're just I'm just saying
you have various options whatever
operating system you want to run.
So what you can do on the VMs?
Okay, let's go back to
computer engine.
Okay, I want need to go back to instance
groups.
Instance groups. I need to go and click
it and then please delete cuz the class
is over and type in here delete.
And that's all it is. This group is all
it is. I just want to make sure he does
get this done. All right.
>> How do we delete it? Because I'm going
to get charged. You just
>> Yeah, you do what I just did. Just
delete it.
What?
Um, I'll be giving a little bit more
homework for this week. I want you guys
to be going over uh instance groups
more. But that's it. I just want to make
sure you guys understand template and
then using the template to make uh
multiple instances.
That's kind of an important part
important thing to understand.
You guys really like that chocolate?
That's Colombian chocolate. No, that's
kind of like
Afro
Afro Venezuelan and Afro Colombian.
That's more AfroColian. I think
>> you referring TIQS's possible.
>> No, Rob's yours.
>> Hold on. What TIQS do?
>> Let's go down. Let me go.
>> He's He's contributing. He's
contributing.
>> Oh,
damn.
Okay, hold on.
That's us. Why can't we have those women
here? Be so nice. Nice black women.
>> Because uh cuz high food to corn syrup.
>> Oh man. The one the one I the one I
>> ask what country she from
>> Ethiopia.
>> There you go.
Can't go wrong over there, man.
Can't go wrong over there.
Mine is Colombian.
So,
come back to Earth. He's drowsy.
>> I I don't know. Like, therapy is the
therapy is kind of It's doing some
things to me. I don't know what's going
on in my mind. Like, what what are you
doing therapy? Like, what's what's
happening? You're
here. This This Mookie is coming out all
of a sudden. Where have you been,
Mookie?
>> He's Mookie's uh been reintroduced to
the world.
Reintroduced to the world. She looks
like a skinny Maya. Yeah. Shout out to
TQS.
>> Yeah. Yeah. TQS. I did go into screen
saver mode.
Wow.
>> Yeah. But That's she that she's for
people who, you know, do their homework
and study in class and wables and all
that fun stuff. All that not fun stuff.
That's boring stuff. Y'all y'all don't
want that. Y'all don't want that. Y'all
y'all like where y'all at. It's all
right.
It's all right.
I'm actually really disciplined this
month. I don't know why.
Totally voted towards leaving the
country. I'm like, you're leaving here.
like you're really going.
It's like
>> you are not sticking around. Whatever it
takes to leave, you got to leave.
>> See, see, you're I I see I recognize you
by your pronouns still. And your
pronouns say that you're crazy enough to
do it. So, I'm not worried about you.
>> You know, I gotta go. I got to get out
of this country. So,
>> I'm having So, okay,
something's going on in the gym market.
I don't know what it is, but if they're
if the gym owners are offering me a lot
of discounts, that means hell's going
on. So, I'm getting like all these
discount just trying to buy equipment
>> and get it refurbished and then get it
on a boat, go to the country. Well, just
well, you can think of it. So, people
don't have money. Discretionary money is
down.
>> It's down a lot,
>> right? So, they're going to start
cutting back. Where do they cut back on?
The fancy gyms. I'm just go plant
fitness. Well, I'm just going buy some
resistance bands on on uh Amazon. I can
do it at home. I'll do it in the park. I
I'll do push-ups, handstand push-ups,
squats. I don't need a I don't need a I
don't need a uh pendulum squat. It's
fancy, but I don't need it. That's what
they're thinking.
So, that's why, you know, people are
closing down. Like, there there are gyms
in my area that were closing down and uh
people were offering their whole setup.
So,
yeah.
>> Yeah.
Yeah. And I guess I'll show you what my
next you talked about pendulum squat.
This is my uh
>> what is it? My June purchase.
This one.
>> Sheesh.
>> Oh no.
>> This is tame,
>> coach. This is the first one. There's
going to be another one.
This is tame.
>> I'll show you the real one.
>> Oh god. Oh, he's going to his he's going
to his fancy one.
Uh
>> yeah, this one.
I've used this one in Austin.
Okay. Yeah. Basically, I use this one.
>> Is that Phil Heath? No, no. This is Pan.
>> Is that Phil Heath? Right. No, the dude.
Is that
>> I think it is. Yeah, it looks like him.
>> Yeah.
>> Number one, baby.
>> Basically, after this thing, I needed a
cigarette.
This was the best pendulum squat I ever
used in my entire life.
>> This was
from heaven, bar none. So, I'm getting
both pendulum squats. So, the first one
is going to be for the general
population people. And for the people
who know what the hell they're doing,
I'm getting this one.
Then, right next to it is going to be
Hold on.
Hold on. Our
This is it. I'm pretty sure this is it.
Super. They did they change it? Yeah,
they changed a little bit. Okay, so this
is a super power squat.
>> Super power.
>> Yeah, I already have a power squat from
Arsenal Strength. It's amazing. I mean,
don't get me wrong, the thing is from
heaven.
>> It's great. This thing, however, though,
you use both of these panadas in
combination. Oh,
so I'm buying these directly from China.
Like get a much greater discount. I
cannot wait to get this and bring it to
Columbia.
>> Just send the address. I'll come to the
gym.
>> Oh yeah. Yeah. I I C coach, I expect you
to be there. Yeah. I coach you to come
in. You want to say like I got a cloud
job and I'll be like, "Hey coach, I
remember you. You get free access to
Berica gym. Come on in."
uh might be a good time to revisit your
your to to restate your gym rules.
>> Okay, so the the the gym rules are
you have to have certifications and then
you have to have a cloud job making six
figures.
If you have those, you can go to Berica
gym anywhere I make it for free. Just
walk in.
I want to make sure you have the card to
make sure you have the access.
this walk in and join and then uh we'll
also give you one free personal
training.
So you can look you can look at personal
trainers I have there choose the hottest
Colombian you want and say I want one
hour with her and then you get personal
training with it for
oh well it's it's on the house we'll
we'll we'll pay for it. Um
though you can see the kind of equipment
that's going to be there.
Um I'll show you another one's going to
be there
but Circ
Yep. That's it. This one.
This is the crown jewel. I've used this
in here in Austin.
I thought I died and went to heaven.
This is the best lat pull down I have
used in my entire life.
I I am building the gym for this machine
alone.
It's that good.
So,
um again, you guys go to the gym abroad
that's going to be there.
plus cards that say that we are part
owners. If you want to have a card
saying you're a part owner, I'll make it
for you.
>> I'm be aware,
>> Kelly, right now it's Kelly. So,
the
making the gym in Brazil is going to be
a pain in the ass.
So, the the first place I'm going to go
to is Cali and make it there. Um,
probably the second place I'll make it
is going to be south of Brazil. Um, but
Brazil it they are [ __ ]
man.
>> I thought you said you weren't even
going to make it in Brazil anymore
because of it.
>> I still want to do it in Brazil. It's
just I cannot do a 2,000 square meter
gym in Brazil and that's not going to
happen. I can do it in Cali.
I can also do it in medigene but it's
20% more in medigene.
>> So Danielle is my chat GPT keeps on
saying if you put this in the meta
machine you're going to have influencers
on there.
You're definitely going to have that
like one guy with the um lesbian haircut
who
whose entire gimmick is how to teach um
guys how to approach Colombian women and
he charges people $3,000 to do that.
>> Uh if if I see a guy in there doing
that, we'll have a little combo because
uh the gym is not going to be a public
gym. It's going to be a semi-private.
And so we do that so that we can screen
a certain demographic.
>> I wonder what demographic we're
screening for.
>> I have no idea.
>> None.
Is Tony Robbins going to be there? No.
No. No. No. Tony Robbins.
Don't don't need no Tony Robbins. Trying
to think what what what cool stuff. Oh,
this is I'll show you one. I'm gonna
have it there. Sorry, next
attack.
Okay,
this machine's good.
This is one of the coolest machines you
can have for posterior itching.
I can't wait to set it up. It's going to
be so cool.
Right.
Yeah. Yeah. Now we're not going to have
any cruel trainers in Colombia.
Effective ones, but not cruel ones then.
Oh, hold on. Um,
will be
double half rack. I show you another
cool one. What do I have?
Let's go images.
Why? Why do we get Why do I get rogue if
I said
you [ __ ]
Okay,
I got a good picture of that. So, this
is it's not a double half. This is just
a half rack. I'm going to have the
double half rack. Means it's going to be
on both sides. So, I'm going to have at
least
um how many stations?
Like 12 stations just for this. And the
reason I want because this this
functional trainer inside is like silk.
I use it here in Austin. It's amazing.
So, I want at least 12 of these
stations, you know, in Columbia.
It's going to be amazing. See you, John.
Are you going to have fitness water
stations and vending machines in your
gym? Uh, we're going to have there will
be filtered water. I already know who
the uh who the vendor is going to be. I
have that written down a piece of paper.
So, actually it's on obsidian. So, I
know the vendor is going to do that. Um,
for the food, there's going to be
another vendor going to come in and do
that for us. Something things up. I
don't want to deal with that to be
honest, but there will be a vendor
coming in um to make uh meal prep meals
for the for anybody who's in there can
order it. We don't I don't I don't think
I'm doing any commission on there
because I don't want to deal with the
commission.
>> Sounds good, man. What? What city in
Cali?
>> Cali.
>> Cali. Colia.
>> Colia.
>> My fault. Okay. Oops.
Okay.
>> City.
>> Nice.
>> So, we here in Cali Columbia.
Anybody here? Anybody know Cali Colia?
>> I do. I It's probably one of my favorite
places. I thought I put it in the strata
one. I know astra this is one right
here.
>> I thought we put it right here.
>> Yeah. All right, cool. You'll get
looted. But you know,
>> part of the fun.
>> So the people who don't do their
homework, you could only go to Bellerica
gym branch office here and this is where
you get shot.
>> I'll be like, you can't do your
homework.
>> Exactly where he circled. Right. I went
I picked up a girl from there. Like I
said, I Uber to pick up a girl from this
area, right? It's been like exactly
where his mouse is right now, actually.
Right. And then the Uber driver said,
"Get this. Make sure this girl comes out
in like two minutes cuz this I am not
going to I am not going to wait here for
more than two minutes." And I knew
>> I noticed they got two hospitals right
there.
>> There's a reason.
>> Yeah, it's So, no, no, I'm not I'm not
going to put it here. I'm going to put
it
>> up through here.
>> Are you going down for Petronial Avarels
this year?
>> What? What? Say it again.
>> Are you going down to Cali for uh the
Afro Festival in August?
>> No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I I I've got
a conclave.
>> Oh, I thought you was doing the con.
Okay. Yeah, that's right. My bad. I
forgot. I'll be down there for that for
my second one, I think.
>> Yeah. So, I'm going We have This whole
area basically is drivable.
>> Yeah.
>> So, I have to land and go find an area.
>> Granada. That's probably where most of
you are going to go your first time to
be honest. Get your first Airbnb.
>> It's going be through here, right?
>> No, Granada is a little bit more south.
That's for like more, you know, like
beginners, but people in the know will
go a little bit more north.
>> Oh, yeah. So, this I thought
What I heard is that this part through
here is boring.
>> Yeah. You didn't No one goes there.
>> Yeah. What I thought.
>> So I want to be
>> go to the north the nor the northern
part, right?
>> Right. Yeah. Five and six here.
>> Right. So that's five and six. Right.
Bario Granada will probably be where a
lot of people are going to get their
first Airbnbs in.
>> Right.
>> In Cali and then Granada north and
northwards. That's where you're going to
get, you know,
just essentially the best, you know, the
best everything in the in the city, you
know.
>> That's why I want I want my gym to be in
this area.
>> Yeah.
>> What be through here?
>> Mhm.
>> I already know how much I'm be charging
per month
where I've I want 400 people. It's my
goal. 400 people, $100 a month. If I can
get that, it' be great.
If I get four, it'll break even if I get
what 150 people at $45 a month.
>> That's um actually that's not bad.
>> Yeah.
>> And then I work for private equity
>> and we had um a gym franchisee, right?
And what's what might happen because
this is what happens in the states is a
lot of people just buy the gym like
equipment but never go. Right. And then
like you have something like half your
people never going but they're giving
you the money anyway. So it's nice for
all the people who do go.
>> Yeah. We're anticipating that. I'm
anticipating there's going to be a lot
of people going to this gym
>> just because I have panata. Panata by
where where's my panata? Okay. So,
Ponata by itself and I I have a Lego as
well.
>> These are going to be the big draws. Um,
this just so you know. So, this CTX,
this is an Arsenal Strength uh clone.
You guys know gym equipment. So, I'm
buying it all the Arsal strength clones
locally. Um, because my friend needs it.
He's not doing well.
Um, but I'm going to bring all this
equipment over here for to Kia. Set it
all up.
You're great.
You have all these
like people saying this is how you
approach women. I was like I can make my
own gym [ __ ] They'll be in my gym.
I don't have to approach it all.
Just I already I already made the
the best way of getting it. Uh do they
still make Versa Climbers? Yes, it's I
have a Versa Climber in my living room.
It's going to be in Cali Columbia.
No goatees allowed in what? Come on. I
don't care if they have a goatee. It's
fine.
Are they building bench? Yeah.
Are the vendors going to make chicken
and waffle meal prep? No. No, they're
not. They're not allowed to do that.
Yo, papa frittas. Nope. Not doing that
either.
How much are the massage rooms in the
back of Baler Rica Gym? I don't know cuz
there won't be any massage parlors in
Baler Rica Gym.
Anyway, Afroch just
to tell you the truth, we're thinking
about putting a booth at Afro to
advertise the Conclave to try to get men
to steal men for God's sake.
Do it.
>> So bad.
>> See you, Elbert.
>> Do it.
>> Club next to the sauna. We're thinking
about putting a sauna in there. I'm I'm
kind of designing it. The big thing that
I learned is that if I don't drop about
$20,000 on the women's bathroom,
>> it's not going to work. The entire gym
will fail.
So, I'm making sure I have $20,000 just
for their bathroom.
>> Really? What? Um,
one, how did you come to that
conclusion? But what is it going to be
in that bathroom? Okay. So,
they have to have I have to have eight
private showers.
>> And then the drainage has got to be able
to not not be cloggable with long hair.
>> Yeah.
>> And then there has to be an area to like
take all the hair out every day. And it
has to be a daily event. Then they have
to sit down and have has to be at least
eight areas where they can sit down and
do their hair, their makeup and
everything like that. Ideally 10
so that the women there so that kind of
starts overflow and then they have to
have locker rooms. Um and then there
what is the big thing is the uh dryers
and the mirrors.
If this isn't done completely correct,
the women will reject the bathroom and
they won't attend the gym.
>> For for the men's gym, for the men's
bathroom, it's simple. I mean, I you
could
like
>> wash there, dress there.
>> No, Theo, we want whatever the ladies
get, we want the same thing.
>> Oh, no. Just Just get some really good
just get some really good walkers. Get
some very good walkers.
>> I want a reclining leather seat.
>> The bros want cigars.
>> You know they need they need light. Yes.
>> Okay.
>> Yes.
>> Alex uh Felder, I already designed the
bathroom.
Designed the bathroom. Sorry. For the
women's area. Already designed it. I
took a European design a European uh
locker room women's locker room. um
re-engineered it. Got all the
instructions about how this be done.
It's the the underneath like the shower,
the the piping, the plumbing, everything
underneath the showers and how it has to
be designed. I got that all designed. I
have all the instructions, everything
ready to go.
Yep.
Yeah. You may get one journal and a
shirt. So, yeah, they they'll be I could
do a private shower for the men. That'll
work. But I don't need to spend 20,000.
I could probably spend 10,000 for the
That'll be good.
So,
yeah. So they need private showers, huge
mirrors, places, sit down, completely
secluded. They also need gossip areas.
That's why I found out
so where they can sit in groups and just
mingle and gossip with each other.
AD Bailey, I could do that.
Yeah. Yeah, I can do that.
Anyway, guys, you can see where I'm
where I'm going with baller gym. Uh,
good class. I enjoyed it. Have some I
had some fun with that. Uh, you guys
doing well. Make sure you do your
homework. I'm going to put some home
assign some more homework onto the
group. So, um, go look at it. If you
guys had questions about the the class
today, make sure you look at the video,
okay? Watch the video. You'll be just
fine. Do not erase your to instance
templates.
You don't get charged for them. Okay?
Keep them going. And on that statement,
I have to go downstairs and complete
bench press. So, I didn't do bench press
today. So, I got to go do that. I have
to do incline bench and incline dumbbell
press. That's going to be all kinds of
fun. I will see you guys later. And good
class. I enjoyed it. See you later. Have
a good night. Yep.